准备好了吗  孩子们
Are you ready, kids?
好了船长
Aye aye, captain
我听不见
I can't hear you
好了船长
Aye aye, captain
是谁住在深海的大菠萝里
Who lives in a pineapple under the sea?
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob SquarePants
方方黄黄伸缩自如
Absorbent and yellow and porous is he
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob SquarePants
如果四处探险是你的愿望
If nautical nonsense be something you wish
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob SquarePants
那就敲敲甲板让大鱼开路
Then drop on the deck and flop like a fish
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob SquarePants
准备
Ready
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob SquarePants
高菲掌勺乐队
编剧
分镜总监
翻译: 1440kHz
动画总监
指导总监
联合监制
监制
客串
本字幕仅限学习交流
严禁用于商业用途
高菲高伯
能再来一份三倍高伯莓黎明吗
Can we get another
Triple Gooberberry Sunrise over here?
三倍的可别不舍得拿出来
And don't you skimp on the triple
你们的黎
Here's your sun--
要开始了
It's starting
我要再来一份
I'll take another one
这次经理加少点
This time with less manager
各位无论多大年纪的小朋友请注意
Attention, children of all ages
你好  嗨
Hello, hi
是我
That's me
我爱你  我爱你
I love you, I love you
多大都行
All ages
请大家鳍声欢迎架子鼓能手
Put your fins together for the cool cat on the drum kit
邦戈熊
Bongos Bear
这只贝壳吹小号的节奏感特别强
On trumpet, this bivalve really swings
蛤蜊克莱
Clem Clam
大家认识他  大家爱他
You know him, you love him
八个触手弹八十八个琴键
Eight tentacles on 88 keys
他就是摇滚普斯
it's Rock T. Puss
这就是我们的乐队
That's our combo
鳍声有请高菲掌勺乐队
Give it up for the Goofy Scoopers
高菲掌勺乐队
一啊二啊三啊四
A one and two and three and four
多来几勺  冰淇淋不少
I need more scoops, ice cream galore
不然我就直接出门走人
Or I'll banana split right out that door
知不知道  我在奏高伯歌
Don't you know, I'm doing the Goober Rag
我爱你  摇滚普斯
I love you, Rock T. Puss
五啊六啊七啊八
Oh, five and six and seven and eight
吃完冰淇淋舔盘子
Finish my ice cream, licking my plate
再来份软糖圣代挺不错
Another fudge sundae sure sounds great
儿童税务
这样就是高伯歌
And that is how I do that Goober Rag
九啊十啊十一十二
Nine and ten and eleven and twelve
架上的朗姆葡萄干拿下来
Get the Rum Raisin off that shelf
一整盒我自个吃光
I'll eat the whole tub all on my own
连蛋筒我都用不着
And I don't even need a cone
知不知道  就是这样
Don't you know, that's how
看清楚  我就在这样
Can't you see, I'm doing it now
我来了  又走了
I'm coming, I'm going
我在奏高伯歌
I'm doing the Goober Rag
好了小朋友  该走了
All right, boys, time to go
不能把我们踢出去
You can't kick us out
我们打小就一直都来这了
We've been coming here since we were kids
对  咱可是高菲掌勺乐队的头号粉丝
Yeah, we're the Goofy Scoopers' biggest fans
那是你们自己的事
Well, that's your problem
都已经打烊了
Closing time
你们可以不用回家
You don't have to go home
但就是不能待在这
but you can't stay here
倒霉透了
This stinks
我本来还想去后台要签名
I wanted to go backstage for an autograph
海绵宝宝
珊迪
妈妈
违停罚单
痞老板到此一游
别发愁了  派大星
Don't worry, Patrick
我们明天就能回来看高菲掌勺乐队了
We'll just come back
and see the Goofy Scoopers tomorrow
法国旁白
第二天早上
早安
Good morning
我身上没钱
I don't carry cash
是你们两个
It's you two
我们一整晚扎营蹲守在外面
We camped out all night
要看高哎掌鞋乐队
to see the Gooey Sneakers
高菲掌勺
Goofy Scoopers
对  他们
Yeah, them
他们要往我头上签名
They're gonna write on my head
那个
Well
关于乐队
about that
高菲掌勺乐队结束了
The Goofy Scoopers are over
太过时了
Too old fashioned
小朋友想要新的声音
The kids want a new sound
新的声音
A new sound?
没错
That's right
我带来了能让你们兴奋的全新表演
I brought in an act you're going to flip over
这位就是
Say hello to
DJ两大勺
DJ 2 Sc00pz
抱歉  冰淇淋主题音乐机器人表演
Sorry, but the Goofy Scoopers are the only
我们只爱高菲掌勺乐队演的
ice cream themed musical robot act we'll ever love
派大星  别被嗡嗡呜呜的曲调迷住了
Patrick, don't give in to its seductive
womp-womps and wub-wubs
求你了  经理先生
Please, Mr. Manager
快告诉我们掌勺乐队在哪
you have to tell us where the Scoopers are
是不是在咖啡厅演出
Are they playing at a coffee house?
是不是在裤头村碗演出
Are they playing the Bikini Bottom Bowl?
还是在世界巡演
Or on a world tour?
天啊  都不是
Oh, my, no
我把那些老旧机器人扔垃圾堆了
I threw those old robots in the garbage
他们再也不会演出了
They're never playing anywhere again
行了  你们把里面气氛都破坏了
All right, you're killing the atmosphere in here
要哭就去外面哭
Please do all your crying outside
闲人免进
等一下  派大星
Wait a minute, Patrick
我有计划了
I have a plan
可以不用哭了
We can stop crying
我才没哭
Well, I wasn't crying
我只是在
I was just
拿水冲我眼睛
flushing my eyes
你刚说什么
You were saying?
我们可以让高菲掌勺乐队复出
We are gonna get the Goofy Scoopers back together
上演重聚秀
for a reunion show
然后大家就都会铭记他们有多伟大了
Then everyone will remember how great they were
可咱连他们在哪都不知道
But we don't know where they are
对
True
不过咱可是知道
but we do know
他们是怎么抵达他们所在的去处的
how they got to where they were
before they went wherever they are
我听不懂
I'm confused
但我很欣赏你的自信
but I appreciate your confidence
加我一个
Count me in
之后
抱歉卡车先借用一下
Sorry about borrowing your truck
我们得去从垃圾堆那里救出机器人
We have to save some robots from the trash
让我们最爱的乐队复出
so our favorite band can get back together
你一定能体谅的
I'm sure you understand
合情合理
That sounds reasonable
垃圾场
你们在对我的宝贝垃圾干什么
What you boys doing to my precious junk?
对不起  先生
Sorry, sir
我只是在找几个机器乐手
I was just looking for some robot musicians
我在找吃的
And I was looking for food
你要吃这根热狗吗
You gonna eat this hot dog?
我完全不懂什么乐手
Well, I don't know nothing about music-men
不过我记得有个机器人来过
but I do remember one robot fella coming through here
大好人
Nice guy
我把他卖给了马戏团  赚了三块五
Sold him to the circus for about $3.50
派大星  我们第一条线索有了
Patrick, it's our first clue
我们得去马戏团
We gotta get to the circus
很好  因为我找到蛋黄酱了
Great, 'cause I just found the mayo
胶水
你在我宝贝垃圾场干什么
What are you doing in my precious junkyard?
马戏团
派大星  是蛤蜊克莱
Patrick, it's Clem Clam
抓住他
Let's get him
等等  派大星
W-w-wait, Patrick
我们来这是跟他交朋友的
We're here to make friends with him
不记得了吗
don't you remember?
很明显我不记得
Obviously, I do not
要怎么办才能让他演出呢
How are we gonna get him to play the show?
有了
I got it
可以用合理论证跟有力论据让他理解
We'll appeal to his intellect
with sound reasoning and convincing arguments
求你了
Please
我们需要你
We need you
你一定要复出  一定要
You gotta come back, you just gotta
别激动  爵士迷
You can cool it, cats
不管你们计划是什么  我都加入
Whatever your scheme is, I'm in
把我从这个疯狂马戏团里救出来就好
Just get me out of this crazy circus
我特别怕小丑
I'm terrified of clowns, man
这就好  蛤蜊克莱先生
Well, that's great, Mr. Clem Clam
因为明天晚上
because tomorrow night
我们要让乐团复出
we're getting the band back together
明晚在高菲高伯上演重聚秀
Reunion show tomorrow night at Goofy Goober's
不过目前为止我只找到了你一个
So far, you're the only one we've found, though
全马戏团身体柔韧性最差的柔术演员
You know, the circus's least flexible contortionist
在市中心那家按摩店看到了邦戈熊
saw Bongos Bear at that massage place downtown, man
是真的
It's true--
太好了
Great
来吧  派大星
come on, Patrick
我又有计划了
I feel another plan forming
等等  带我一起去
Wait, take me with you, man
按摩
是的
Yes
我跟我老婆来这做夫妻按摩
my wife and I are here for the couples massage
话说
Say
你不是高菲掌勺乐队那位邦戈熊吗
aren't you Bongos Bear from the Goofy Scoopers?
你找错机器熊了
Son, you got the wrong robot bear
我连音乐都不喜欢
I don't even like music
只做按摩
I just give massages
屁股也得按摩哦
Don't forget to work my glutes
好了好了  你们赢了
All right, all right, you win
我就是邦戈熊
I am Bongos Bear
我冷冰冰的机器内心热爱音乐
And I got music in my cold, robotic heart
那你可走运了
Well, you're in luck
我跟派大星要让你们乐队复出
'cause Patrick and I
are getting your band back together
是啊  可我们还得找到钢琴章鱼
Yeah, but we still gotta find the piano octopus
那简单
That's easy
有个腰疼的建筑工人告诉我
A construction worker with lumbago told me
摇滚现在在贝壳城的大桥工作
Rock is working on the bridge to Shell City now
是真的
It's true--
摇滚
Rock?
摇滚普斯
Rock T. Puss?
太烂了
This stinks
邦戈骗了我们
Bongos lied
我根本没看到他在
I don't see him anywhere
快点走开
Get out of here
我在干活呢
I'm on the job
摇滚普斯
Rock T. Puss
我们是海绵宝宝跟派大星
we're SpongeBob and Patrick
是你的头号粉丝
we're your biggest fans
才怪
Yeah, right
没人记得我的音乐
No one remembers my music
没事
That's okay
我什么都不记得
I don't remember anything
听着  小朋友
Look, kids
我现在是工程作业机器人
I'm a working robot now
我唯一关心的队
The only bands I care about
只有过桥的船只
are the boats on this bridge
船的鸣笛声才是我需要的掌声
Their honking horns
are the only applause I'll ever need again
我发的声音
That was me
抱歉  都是热狗害的
Sorry, I blame the hot dog
求你了  普斯先生
Please, Mr. Puss
我们要让高菲掌勺乐队复出
We're getting the Goofy Scoopers back together
上演重聚秀
for a reunion show
我们需要你
We need you
这种事免谈
The answer is no
我现在是座桥
I'm a bridge now
快点走开
Get out of here
高菲高伯
爵士迷们
Hey, cats
摇滚在哪
Where's Rock?
他不来了
He's not coming
什么
Wha?
没摇滚普斯  都不知道表演能不能成
I don't know if we can do this without Rock T. Puss
放心  我们跟你们一起演出
Don't worry, we'll be playing with you
会很有意思的
It'll be fun
这是我写的新歌
Here's the new piece I wrote
一开场就迅速进入状态
We're gonna come in hot off the intro
尽量跟上节奏
so try to keep up
冰淇淋  好好吃
Ice cream, so tasty
冰到嘴巴里
Freezing in my mouth
脑子冻得特别疼
Icy pain inside my brain
能不能救救我
Won't you help me out?
我大脑结冰  我大脑结冰
I have a brain freeze, I have a brain freeze
我大脑结冰  快来救救我吧
I have a brain freeze, help me with my brain freeze
我能不能再来一份圣代
Can I have another sundae, please?
观众全都不喜欢
They are not digging it, man
都交代过你们要跟上节奏的
We told you guys to keep up
摇滚普斯  你来了
Rock T. Puss, you came
抱歉让你们久等了
Sorry I left you hanging, guys
我确实喜欢当桥
I did like being a bridge
但我生来就要创作音乐
But I was built to make music
话说桥怎么样了
Say, how is the bridge?
肯定没事的
I'm sure its fine
一起摇滚吧
Now, let's rock
小朋友还是不喜欢
The kids still don't like it
该怎么办
What do we do?
也许我可以帮忙
Maybe I can help with that
在下DJ两大勺
I'm DJ 2 Sc00pz
是高菲掌勺乐队的铁粉
and I'm a huge Goofy Scoopers fan
要来狂欢吗
Care to jam?
最棒的高菲掌勺乐队秀
Best Goofy Scoopers show ever
本集完
派大狗
编剧
分镜总监
翻译: 1440kHz
动画总监
联合监制
监制
本字幕仅限学习交流
严禁用于商业用途
动物收容所
办公室
喂  动物管理局
Hello, animal control
马文
海绵宝宝  我很感谢你
SpongeBob, I appreciate you
来动物收容所做志愿
volunteering here at the animal shelter
可你能不能别再让虫子用电话了
but could you please
stop letting the worms use the phone?
我交代过它们不要再叫外卖了
I told them no more takeout calls
儿童餐
好  需要什么帮助
Now, how can I help you?
我家外面有条虫子
There's a worm somewhere outside my house
叫个没完没了
and it won't stop barking
我这就过去处理
I'll get on that right away
我得去抓流浪动物了
I gotta go catch a stray
海绵宝宝  你来帮我管收容所
SpongeBob, you hold down the fort
是的  长官
Sir, yes, sir
我会尽力照顾好这些野虫子的
I will take care of these wild worms
to the best of my ability
刽子手
关刽子手的笼子
B-B-Butcher's cage
刽子手
Butcher?
我知道你是个乖孩子
I know you're really a good boy
让我摸摸你
Just let me pet you
轻轻摸
real gentle
真乖
That a boy
希望它吃海绵还没吃习惯
I hope he doesn't develop a taste for sponge
动物收容所
派大星
Patrick
好耶
Yeah
谁是乖孩子
Who's a good boy?
派大星是我朋友
Patrick's my friend
有时候他不小心吃了虫粮
Sometimes if he's eaten worm food by mistake
就会切换成虫子模式
he's goes into worm mode
不知道会持续多长时间
There's no telling how long it'll last
要是他在几天之内没被训好
Well, if he's not trained in a few days
达到可以被收养的标准
so he can be adopted
就必须要锁进笼子里
he'll have to be locked up
跟刽子手一样
like Butcher
你放心  先生
Don't worry, sir
我会训好他的
I'll train him
他已经会定点排便了
He's already housebroken
我就知道他排了
I knew he was broken
还以为能定点
I thought it was house
派大星
Now, Patrick
每条乖虫子都要学会做训练动作
every good worm needs to learn how to do tricks
学得好就可以奖励虫粮
Then they get wormy treats as a reward
坐
Sit
就差一点
Almost
再试另外一个动作
Let's try another one
握手
Shake
试试翻滚看看吧
Shall we try roll over?
派大星  等等
Patrick, wait
地铁
翻滚海星快车  准时到达
Rolling Star Express, right on time
有条小虫该去洗澡了
I know one wormy that needs a bath
好  好
Okay, okay
不洗澡  不洗澡
no bath, no bath
来吧  派大星
Here, Patrick
虫子之间要互相学习
Worms learn from other worms
它们可以教你学乖
They'll show you how to be a good boy
一小时后
终点
这条虫子危害巨大
This worm is a menace
恐怕他只能锁在笼子里了
I'm afraid he'll have to be locked up
跟刽子手一样
like Butcher
求求你别这样
Please don't do that
我来收养他
I'll adopt him
我来带他回家
I'll take him home
让我来救他
He'll be my rescue
你会对他负起全部责任吗
And you'll take full responsibility for him?
我保证
I promise
那就好
Well, that's good
反正我不是很想把他恢复原状
I really didn't want to have to fix him, anyway
谢谢  谢谢
Thank you, thank you
派大星
Patrick
慢点
Whoa, boy
跟上
Heel
抱歉
Sorry
小蜗
Oh, Gary
我给你带了个玩伴回来
I brought you a playmate
派大星  小蜗
Patrick, Gary
不  住手
No, stop
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob
快点
Come on
对不起
I'm sorry
吵到你了吗
Was the noise bothering you?
派大星  跟上
Patrick, heel
天啊
Jeez
听好
Look
我不稀罕你们开的什么破烂怪派对
I don't care what kind of
weird and stupid parties you throw
我只要你让你宠物安静消停点
I'm just asking that you keep your pet quiet
我已经没办法了
I am at my wit's end
派大星又变成虫子模式了
Patrick is in worm mode again
可这回他失控了
But this time, he's out of control
是条虫子都能训好
Any worm can be tamed
连派大星那样傻的都能训
Even one as dumb as Patrick
他只是需要严格教导
He just needs tough love
你会严格教导派大星吗  章鱼哥
Would you tough-love Patrick, Squidward?
休想
No way
求你了  章鱼哥
Please, Squidward
你肯定是最强的训虫师了
I bet you're the best worm trainer ever
拜托
Please
朝我作揖
Beg me
好  坐下
Okay, sit
我可真是个上好训傻师
Well, I'm a good idiot trainer
既然派大星是个傻子
And since Patrick's an idiot
好  我这就去训练他
Okay, I'll train him
但你得先装死
But only if you play dead--
继续装下去
And stay playing dead
我得去训练傻子了
I've got an idiot to train
先从简单的开始训起
We'll start with something simple
训虫方法
我来教你尾随我
I'll teach you how to heel
现在
Now
乖乖听话
be a good boy
跟上
Heel--
停
stop
跟上
Heel
好  都够了
All right, that's it
呛呛欢迎你来到
海草林
祝你幸福
Have a nice life
嗨  章鱼哥
Hi, Squidward
我还在装死
I'm still playing dead
严格教导
Tough love
这个  我的爱叫小朋友
This, my little barking friend
是电击项圈
is a shock collar
每次你一叫  我就会按按钮
Whenever you bark, I'll push this button
给你轻轻地严厉电一下
and give you a mild tough-love shock
没反应
Nothing?
一定是坏了
It must be broken
该死
Nuts
还在装死
Still playing dead
不好意思  章鱼哥先生
Excuse me, Mr. Squidward
海绵宝宝告诉我
SpongeBob tells me
你用严格教导来训好了派大星
that you've trained Patrick using tough love
派大星
Patrick?
他无药可救
He's impossible
我本来要教他坐下
I've tried to get him to sit--
好  然后我教他站起来作揖
Okay, well, then I tried to get him to beg--
转圈
Spin
握手
Now shake
啦啦队式劈叉
Cheerleader split
变成鸡
Chicken
变成鸡块
Chicken nugget
假装弹吉他
Air guitar
现在装死
Now play dead
什么
What?
你做到了
You did it
你创造了奇迹
You're a miracle worker
不是我吹牛  这可
Well, I don't like to brag, but--
太厉害了
That's great
有条特别麻烦的虫子需要你来训
We've got a problem worm that needs training
什么
What?
大家把它带进来
Bring him in, fellas
动物管理局
这位就是刽子手
Say hello to Butcher
跟上  跟上
Heel, heel
停
Stop--
跟上  跟上
heel, heel--
去捡
fetch
跟上  跟上
heel, heel
你不是虫子了
You're not a worm anymore
我几小时前就恢复原状了
Nah, I snapped out of it hours ago
我只是想让章鱼哥
I just wanted Squidward
自我感觉良好而已
to feel like he did a good job
好了  都够了
All right, that's enough
我要给你来点教训
I'll teach you
是啊  希望章鱼哥没对它太严了
Yeah, I hope Squidward's not too tough on him
坐不坐
Will you sit?
不行
don't
下午好  先生
Good afternoon, gentlemen
好个散步遛狗的好日子
Nice day for a walk